My previous training is the BUT Informatique (Data specialty) at the IUT in Reims. 
What I can say in positive is that most of the teachers are very nice and the classes are mostly interesting. Teachers are accessible and human, very few assignments due to the fact that the days are well-organized and busy. I understood the different things discussed during the courses thanks to the explanations and the TPs.
However, on the negative side, there are far too many communication courses for what it pays in the end. The AI courses taken in the last year are not prepared by the teachers concerned, thus causing boredom during these courses. Some courses or subjects are very little useful because we learn very little or it is very little useful to us. One of the professors gave us articles that we used as a course, except it is not supposed to be considered a course because there is no added value. Finally, in the last year, there is still web development while I specialize in data.

In short, despite all the negative points, my training at IUT went very well and I loved being there.
