I am currently a master's student in computer science, specializing in artificial intelligence, at the University of Reims. Prior to this, I studied artificial intelligence engineering and data science in Algeria, where I gained strong skills in deep learning, machine learning, natural language processing (NLP), and data science. I had the opportunity to work on several interesting projects. This year, I am highly motivated to continue my education in a promising environment that aligns with my professional goals. I also appreciate the quality of the courses taught by competent professors, which makes the learning experience even more enriching.
